Malaya
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Malaya
2.1.3.1.1.5
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1497
- Malaya, 2.1.3.1.1.5
  - Malaya, 1921; 27 (Box 1497)
    - Lahat Valley, two hydraulic monitors, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 28 (Box 1497)
    - Lahat Mine, one hydraulic monitor, side view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 29 (Box 1497)
    - Two Sakei[Sakai] men with blowpipe, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 30 (Box 1497)
    - Old Sakei[Sakai] man, full figure, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 31 (Box 1497)
    - Old Sakei[Sakai] man, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 32 (Box 1497)
    - Sakei[Sakai] beauty holding baby, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 33 (Box 1497)
    - Sakei[Sakai] beauty, not smiling, holding baby, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 34 (Box 1497)
    - Old Sakei[Sakai] woman pounding betel nut, side view (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 35 (Box 1497)
    - Old Sakei[Sakai] woman pounding betel nut, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 36 (Box 1497)
    - Old Sakei[Sakai] woman pounding betel nut, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 37 (Box 1497)
    - Old woman chewing betel nut (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 38 (Box 1497)
    - Sunrise over sea near Duncan Roberts's bungalow, low tide, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 39 (Box 1497)
    - Large junk with three sails, steamer in distance (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 40 (Box 1497)
    - Large junk with three sails, small portion of stern of steamer showing on left (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 41 (Box 1497)
    - Large junk with three sails, two sail junk on left (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 42 (Box 1497)
    - Large junk with three sails, masts of junks and large sailing ships in distance (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 43 (Box 1497)
    - Naked boy with rice stomach, hand on mouth, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 44 (Box 1497)
    - Old Chinese man with baby on knee, his wife at his side, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 45 (Box 1497)
    - Small feet of a Chinese woman, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 46 (Box 1497)
    - Fat Chinese shopkeeper, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 47 (Box 1497)
    - Coolie eating with chopsticks, laughing, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 48 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker pushing pill in pipe (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 49 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker, close-up, pipe over lamp, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 50 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker sleeping, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 51 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker, sitting up, holding pipe (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 52 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker, sitting up, not holding pipe (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 53 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker, lying down, rolling pill on pipe bowl, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 54 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker, lying down, holding pipe close to lamp (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 55 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker holding pipe over lamp (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 56 (Box 1497)
    - Opium smoker's hand, pipe and lamp, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 57 (Box 1497)
    - United States sailors in Chinatown, Lowell Thomas wearing topee [pith helmet] in foreground, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 58 (Box 1497)
    - Chinese temple, no lamppost or lumber on right, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 59 (Box 1497)
    - Chinese temple with garden in Penang, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 60 (Box 1497)
    - Travellers Palm, Eastern and Oriental Hotel in Penang (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 61 (Box 1497)
    - Travellers Palm, Eastern and Oriental hotel in Penang, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 62 (Box 1497)
    - Turtles at Chinese garden in temple, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 63 (Box 1497)
    - River in Malacca, one sail boat, one row boat, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 64 (Box 1497)
    - River in Malacca, two boats with sails unfurled, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 65 (Box 1497)
    - A Malacca bullock cart, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 66 (Box 1497)
    - Man with monkey, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 67 (Box 1497)
    - Man with monkey drinking from the coconut, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 68 (Box 1497)
    - Man with monkey eating coconut out of man's hand, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 69 (Box 1497)
    - Monkey climbing tree, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 70 (Box 1497)
    - Monkey climbing tree, near view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 71 (Box 1497)
    - Two monkeys quarreling over coconut, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 72 (Box 1497)
    - Yang Tuan of Negri Sembilan, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 73 (Box 1497)
    - Honorable W. G. Maxwell, Chief Secretary talking to Malay boy, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 74 (Box 1497)
    - Honorable W. G. Maxwell and Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 75 (Box 1497)
    - Honorable W. G. Maxwell, Three Quarter length, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 76 (Box 1497)
    - Honorable W. G. Maxwell, bust, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 77 (Box 1497)
    - Men sliding down a rock in Kuala Lumpur, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 78 (Box 1497)
    - Group of men sliding down a rock, goat in foreground (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso: Mengglanchior - rock slide, with group of people descending, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 79 (Box 1497)
    - Sultan of Perak and Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 80 (Box 1497)
    - Sultan, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Mrs. Bernard at tea, Mr. Craighton standing (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
    - Sultan, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Mrs. Bernard at tea, Mr. Craighton standing (Graphlex), 2
  - Malaya, 1921; 81 (Box 1497)
    - Sultan and Lowell Thomas looking at each other, servant holding umbrella over Sultan, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 82 (Box 1497)
    - Sultan's tea party, H.H. not looking at camera, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table, 1
  - Malaya, 1921; 83 (Box 1497)
    - Sultan and horse, close-up, 1
  - Malaya, 1921; 84 (Box 1497)
    - Houseboat, Lowell Thomas seated at table, 1
    - Note: L.T. writing on his boat, while navigating the murky rivers of the Malay Jungle, 2
    - Verso: L.T. writing at table on the deck of a Malay houseboat, to the rhythm of the native peddlers
  - Malaya, 1921; 85 (Box 1497)
    - Dead boatman, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  Box 1498
- Malaya, 2.1.3.1.1.5
  - Malaya, 1921; 1 (Box 1498)
    - Dead boatman, slightly side face, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 2 (Box 1498)
    - Pilot of house boat, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 3 (Box 1498)
    - Pilot of houseboat, slightly side face, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 4 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley, "White Raja of Perak "and Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 5 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley, "White Raja of Perak," in saddle, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 6 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley, "White Raja of Perak ," on horse, more distant view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 7 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley, "White Raja of Perak ," standing near horse, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 8 (Box 1498)
    - Mill and falls near Captain Hubert Berkeley's bungalow, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 9 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley feeding bananas to a bullock, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 10 (Box 1498)
    - Small black monkey being held, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 11 (Box 1498)
    - Monkey hanging from bough, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 12 (Box 1498)
    - Monkey hanging from bough with one hand, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 13 (Box 1498)
    - Monkey clinging to little girl, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 14 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley and elephants in front of bungalow, children standing, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 15 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley and elephants in front of bungalow, children squatting, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 16 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley and elephants in front of bungalow, children sitting in front, man wearing helmet in distance, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 17 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley slightly turned, with elephants and people surrounding, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 18 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley in front of 110 year old elephant, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 19 (Box 1498)
    - Captain Hubert Berkeley in front of 110 year old elephant, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 20 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant kneeling, man on head, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 21 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant kneeling, no man on head, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 22 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant kneeling, man standing alongside, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 23 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant standing with man standing by trunk, side view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 24 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant standing with man standing alongside, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 25 (Box 1498)
    - Elephant standing with man sitting on top, reflected in stagnant pool, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 26 (Box 1498)
    - Two elephants rubbing trunks, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 27 (Box 1498)
    - Two Elephants rubbing trunks, not so good, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 28 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants bathing, branches of tree on left, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 29 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants bathing - branches on left - (not so good as 8-960), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 30 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants bathing, close-up, no branches, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 31 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants bathing, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 32 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants swimming upstream, mountain in distance, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 33 (Box 1498)
    - String of elephants in river starting ashore, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 34 (Box 1498)
    - String of elephants in river, midstream, best view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 35 (Box 1498)
    - Wild elephants grazing, scattered, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 36 (Box 1498)
    - Wild elephants grazing, in a close group, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 37 (Box 1498)
    - Haji, close-up, serious, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 38 (Box 1498)
    - Haji, close-up, laughing, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 39 (Box 1498)
    - Harry Chase and Lowell Thomas at meal, elephants coming, 1
    - Verso: An elephant coming to pay his respects to our little dinner party. "Lal-ji" comes for his morning tea and toast, 1-verso
    - Harry Chase and Lowell Thomas at meal, elephants coming, 2
    - Verso: L. T. and Chase at meal - elephant coming out of jungle, 2-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 40 (Box 1498)
    - Harry Chase, Lowell Thomas, and 18 Elephants, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 41 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas in howdah, trunk up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 42 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas crossing river on elephant, distant view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 43 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas crossing river on elephant, nearer view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 44 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas crossing river on elephant, row of boats on left, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 45 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas crossing river on elephant, trunk up, side view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 46 (Box 1498)
    - Lowell Thomas crossing river on elephant, trunk up, houseboat in background, front view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 47 (Box 1498)
    - Elephants bathing, boat and branches, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 48 (Box 1498)
    - One elephant bathing with one boat on left, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 49 (Box 1498)
    - Woman sitting on prostrate elephants, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 50 (Box 1498)
    - "Get ready, go!" Cock fight scene, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 51 (Box 1498)
    - Victor of cock fight, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 52 (Box 1498)
    - Old Malay with protruding jaw, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 53 (Box 1498)
    - Young Raja with gun at shoulder, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 54 (Box 1498)
    - Laughing Malay holding spear and kris, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 55 (Box 1498)
    - Serious Malay holding spear, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 56 (Box 1498)
    - Laughing, toothless Malay holding spear, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 57 (Box 1498)
    - Malay with kris in dancing pose, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 58 (Box 1498)
    - Malay holding beautifully-colored bird, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 59 (Box 1498)
    - Malay girl laughing, face only, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 60 (Box 1498)
    - Malay girl, side view, head and shoulders only, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 61 (Box 1498)
    - Malay woman in conical hat, baby in sling, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 62 (Box 1498)
    - Malay woman without hat, baby in sling, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 63 (Box 1498)
    - Malay padi farmer's home, 20 people in foreground, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 64 (Box 1498)
    - Chinese peddler at Kuba Road (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 65 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil Dance, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 66 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil band dancing, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 67 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil band dancing, slightly better, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 68 (Box 1498)
    - Linnell and Tamil dancer, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 69 (Box 1498)
    - Little Tamil dancer holding pole, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 70 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil dancer with spotted face, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 71 (Box 1498)
    - Man imitating woman, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 72 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil dancer, one hand up, one on hip, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 73 (Box 1498)
    - Tamil dancer, arms extended, fists clenched, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 74 (Box 1498)
    - Tiny Tamil wearing coat only, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 75 (Box 1498)
    - Three small Tamils, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  Box 1499
- Malaya, 2.1.3.1.1.5
  - Malaya, 1921; 1 (Box 1499)
    - Tiny Tamil girl with long ear lobes, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 2 (Box 1499)
    - Small Tamil boy with long ear lobes, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 3 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil baby wearing heart behind, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 4 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil baby sitting down, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 5 (Box 1499)
    - Party including Lowell Thomas, in group with Sakais, Harry Chase squatting on right, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 6 (Box 1499)
    - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Sakai girl, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 7 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai belle with dagger, front view, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 8 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai belle leaning against tree, lighting cigarette, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 9 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai belle leaning against tree, smoking, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 10 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai belle, close-up of head, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 11 (Box 1499)
    - Second Sakai belle with cigarette, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 12 (Box 1499)
    - Old Sakai woman laughing with cloth in hand, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 13 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai woman with cloth on shoulder, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 14 (Box 1499)
    - Two Sakai women in loin clothes, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 15 (Box 1499)
    - Two Sakai women in loin clothes, standing nearer together, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 16 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai boy getting light from smoking brother, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 17 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai boy getting light from brother, taller boy stooping, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 18 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai in boats, man in prow looking toward camera, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 19 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai in boats, man in prow not looking at camera, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 20 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai hill tribe of upper Perak under bamboo lean-to, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 21 (Box 1499)
    - Girl with splint through nose holding baby and leaf (Graphlex), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 22 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai man, three children and woman with bamboo through nose, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 23 (Box 1499)
    - Sakai man's head, side view, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 24 (Box 1499)
    - Lowell Thomas and boat crew on Perak River standing, close-up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 25 (Box 1499)
    - Shooting rapids, Lowell Thomas and crew with backs turned, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 26 (Box 1499)
    - Shooting rapids, nearer view, large rock, Lowell Thomas and crew with backs turned, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 27 (Box 1499)
    - Shooting rapids, side view of Lowell Thomas, smoking pipe, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 28 (Box 1499)
    - Shooting rapids, front view of Lowell Thomas smoking pipe, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 29 (Box 1499)
    - Shooting rapids, oarsmen in foreground, smaller boat in distance, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 30 (Box 1499)
    - River, oarsmen in foreground, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 31 (Box 1499)
    - Houseboat, close-up under tree, Lowell Thomas on deck, elephant bathing nearby, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 32 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber plantation, Lowell Thomas walking along roadway, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 33 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber plantation, man tapping tree, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 34 (Box 1499)
    - Panorama of rubber plantation, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 35 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber tapping, distant, pouring, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 36 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber tapping, close-up, pouring, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 37 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber, woman and girl tapping, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 38 (Box 1499)
    - Rubber, woman tapping, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 39 (Box 1499)
    - Two Englishmen and six Tamils covered with white mud, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 40 (Box 1499)
    - Five Tamils covered with white mud, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 41 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil, head up and on one side, covered with white mud, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 42 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil, close-up, head only, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 43 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil with black face and white body, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 44 (Box 1499)
    - Tamil covered with white mud, three quarter length looking straight at camera, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 45 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 46 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap squatting beside crocodile, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 47 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap carrying crocodile on pole, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 48 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap standing in boat shooting at crocodiles, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 49 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap standing in boat shooing at crocodiles, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 50 (Box 1499)
    - "Tiger" Manap standing in boat shooting at crocodiles (Lowell Thomas note: Negative slightly light-struck), 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 51 (Box 1499)
    - Lowell Thomas standing in boat shooting at crocodiles in mangrove swamp, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 52 (Box 1499)
    - Lowell Thomas standing in boat cranking motion picture camera in mangrove swamp, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 53 (Box 1499)
    - Panorama of mangrove swamp, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 54 (Box 1499)
    - Mangrove tree, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 55 (Box 1499)
    - Man holding leopard with head down, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 56 (Box 1499)
    - Man holding leopard with head up, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 57 (Box 1499)
    - Four tigers, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 58 (Box 1499)
    - Three tigers, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 59 (Box 1499)
    - Two tigers, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 60 (Box 1499)
    - One tiger lying stretched out, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 61 (Box 1499)
    - One tiger, side view of head, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 62 (Box 1499)
    - Road to Pahang from Kuala Kuba, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 63 (Box 1499)
    - Tin sluice boxes in mountain stream, near Kuala Kuba, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 64 (Box 1499)
    - Sunset, lone palm tree, mountain in distance, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 65 (Box 1499)
    - Taiping Hill from government building grounds, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 66 (Box 1499)
    - Tin dredge, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 67 (Box 1499)
    - Crowd watching Harry Chase taking pictures, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 68 (Box 1499)
    - Gordon Morse receiving curtain lecture from Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 69 (Box 1499)
    - Colonel Fillis on rearing horse, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 70 (Box 1499)
    - Chinese junk near island, distant view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 71 (Box 1499)
    - Chinese junk near island, near view, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 72 (Box 1499)
    - Sunset over mountains, Ipoh Railway Hotel, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso
  - Malaya, 1921; 73 (Box 1499)
    - Sunset over mountains, Ipoh Railway Hotel, oblong shaped cloud in middle of sky on left, 1
    - Verso, 1-verso